Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Daily Report, Job 490, 1978, 3 of 3,1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 491,1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 491,1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 492, 1978, 1 of 3,1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 492, 1978, 2 of 3,1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 492, 1978, 3 of 3,1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 492, 1979, 1 of 3,1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 492, 1979, 2 of 3,1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 492, 1979, 3 of 3,1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 493, 1978, 1 of 2,1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 493, 1978, 2 of 2,1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 493,1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 494,1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 494,1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 495,1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 498,1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 499,1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 500,1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 501,1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 501,1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 502,1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 502,1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Daily Report, Job 503, 1979, 1 of 5,1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 503, 1979, 2 of 5,1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 503, 1979, 3 of 5,1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 503, 1979, 4 of 5,1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 503, 1979, 5 of 5,1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 504, 1979, 1 of 3,1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 504, 1979, 2 of 3,1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 504, 1979, 3 of 3,1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 505,1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 506,1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 507, 1979, 1 of 3,1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 507, 1979, 2 of 3,1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 507, 1979, 3 of 3,1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 508,1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 510,1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 511,1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1979, 1 of 4,1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1979, 2 of 4,1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1979, 3 of 4,1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1979, 4 of 4,1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 1 of 7,1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 2 of 7,1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 3 of 7,1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 4 of 7,1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 5 of 7,1980 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 6 of 7,1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 512, 1980, 7 of 7,1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 513,1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 513,1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 514,1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 515,1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 516,1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 517,1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 521,1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 523,1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 524,1979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 524,1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Daily Report, Job 526,1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Daily Report, Job 527, 1 of 2,1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 527, 2 of 2,1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 527,1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 528,1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 529,1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 530,1980 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 536,1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 536,1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 537, 1 of 2,1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 537, 2 of 2,1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 538,1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 539,1 of 4,1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 539,2 of 4,1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 539,3 of 4,1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 539,4 of 4,1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 539,1981 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 540,1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 542,1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 543,1981 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 544,1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 545,1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 545,1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 545,1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 546.1 of 6,1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 546. 2 of 6,1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 546. 3 of 6,1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 546. 4 of 6,1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 546. 5 of 6,1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 546. 6 of 6,1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 547.1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 548,1981 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 549,1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 550,1981 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 551, 1 of 31981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 551, 2 of 31981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 551, 3 of 31981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 1 of 4,1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 2 of 4,1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 3 of 4,1981 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 4 of 4,1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 1 of 8,1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 2 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 3 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 4 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 5 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 6 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 7 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 552, 8 of 8,1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 553, 1 of 2,1981 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 553, 2 of 2,1981 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 555, 1 of 2,1981 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 555, 2 of 2,1981 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 556,1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 557,1981 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 558,1981 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 558, 1 of 2,1982 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 558, 2 of 2,1981 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 559,1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 560, 1 of 3,1981 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 560, 2 of 3,1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 560, 3 of 3,1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 560,1982 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 561, 1 of 2,1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 561, 2 of 2,1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 562,1982 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 563,1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 563, 1 of 2,1982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 563, 2 of 2,1982 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 564,1982 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 565,1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 566,1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 567,1982 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 568,1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 569,1982 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 570,1982 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 571,1982 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 572, 1 of 2,1983 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 572, 2 of 2,1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 573,1982 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 574, 1 of 3,1982 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 574, 2 of 3,1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 574, 3 of 3,1982 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 575,1982 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 576, 1 of 2,1982 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 576, 2 of 2,1982 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 577,1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 577, 1 of 2,1983 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 577, 2 of 2,1983 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 577, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 577, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 578,1982 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 579,1982 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 580,1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 581,1982 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 582, 1 of 5,1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 582, 2 of 5,1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 582, 3 of 5,1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 582, 4 of 5,1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 582, 5 of 5,1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 582,1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 584,1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 584,1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 585,1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 586,1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 587, 1 of 2,1983 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 587, 2 of 2,1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 588, 1 of 2,1983 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 588, 2 of 2,1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 589,1983 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 1 of 4,1983 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 2 of 4,1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 3 of 4,1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 4 of 4,1983 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 1 of 6,1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 2 of 6,1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 3 of 6,1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 4 of 6,1984 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 5 of 6,1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 590, 6 of 6,1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 590,1985 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 591,1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 592,1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 592,1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 593,1983 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 593,1984 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 594,1983 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 595,1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 595,1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 596,1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 596, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 596, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 597, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 597, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 599,1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 600, 1 of 3,1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 600, 2 of 3,1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 600, 3 of 3,1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 601,1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 602, 1 of 4,1984 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 602, 2 of 4,1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 602, 3 of 4,1984 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 602, 4 of 4,1984 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 603,1984 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 604,1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 605,1984 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 606, 1 of 5,1984 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 606, 2 of 5,1984 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 606, 3 of 5,1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 606, 4 of 5,1984 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 606, 5 of 5,1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 607, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 607, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 608,1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 1 of 8,1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 2 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 3 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 4 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 5 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 6 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 7 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 608, 8 of 8,1985 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 608,1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 609,1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 609,1985 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 610,1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 610,1985 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 611, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 611, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 612,1985 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 613,1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 614, 1 of 2,1984 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 614, 2 of 2,1984 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 614, 1 of 2,1985 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 614, 2 of 2,1985 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 1 of 8,1985 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 2 of 8,1985 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 3 of 8,1985 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 4 of 8,1985 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 5 of 8,1985 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 6 of 8,1985 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 7 of 8,1985 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 8 of 8,1985 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 615, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 617,1985 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 618,1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 619,1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 620, 1 of 3,1985 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 620, 2 of 3,1985 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 620, 3 of 3,1985 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 621,1985 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 622, 1 of 3,1985 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 622, 2 of 3,1985 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 622, 3 of 3,1985 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 623,1985 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 624,1985 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 624, 1 of 5,1986 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 624, 2 of 5,1986 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 624, 3 of 5,1986 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 624, 4 of 5,1986 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 624, 5 of 5,1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 625, 1 of 3,1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 625, 2 of 3,1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 625, 3 of 3,1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 626,1985 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 627,1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 628,1987 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 1 of 5,1985 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 2 of 5,1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 3 of 5,1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 4 of 5,1985 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 5 of 5,1985 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 629, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 630,1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 631,1986 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 632,1986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 6331986 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 634, 1 of 4,1986 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 634, 2 of 4,1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 634, 3 of 4,1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 634, 4 of 4,1986 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 634,1987 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 635,1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 636,1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 637,1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 638,1986 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 638,1987 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 639, 1 of 2,1986 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 639, 2 of 2,1986 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 640, 1 of 3,1986 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 640, 2 of 3,1986 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 640, 3 of 3,1986 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 640, 1 of 2,1987 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 640, 2 of 2,1987 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 641, 1 of 6,1986 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 641, 2 of 6,1986 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 641, 3 of 6,1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 641, 4 of 6,1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 641, 5 of 6,1986 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 641, 6 of 6,1986 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 643, 1 of 4,1987 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 643, 2 of 4,1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 643, 3 of 4,1987 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 643, 4 of 4,1987 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 644,1987 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 1 of 9,1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 2 of 9,1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 3 of 9,1987 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 4 of 9,1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 5 of 9,1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 6 of 9,1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 7 of 9,1987 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 8 of 9,1987 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 644, 9 of 9,1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 645,1987 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 646,1987 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 647,1987 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 648,1987 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 649,1987 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 650,1987 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 651,1987 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 652,1987 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 653,1987 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 654,1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 654,1988 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 655,1987 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 656,1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 657,1988 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 657, 1 of 5,1988 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 657, 2 of 5,1988 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 657, 3 of 5,1988 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 657, 4 of 5,1988 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 657, 5 of 5,1988 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 657,1989 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 658, 1 of 2,1987 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 658, 2 of 2,1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 658,1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 659,1988 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 660,1987 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 660,1988 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 661,1987 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 661, 1 of 3,1988 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 661, 2 of 3,1988 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 661, 3 of 3,1988 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 661,1989 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 662,1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 663,1988 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 664, 1 of 3,1988 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 664, 2 of 3,1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 664, 3 of 3,1988 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 664, 1 of 3,1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 664, 2 of 3,1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 664, 3 of 3,1989 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 664,1990 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 665,1988 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 666, 1 of 3,1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 666, 2 of 3,1988 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 666, 3 of 3,1988 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 667,1988 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 667,1989 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 668, 1 of 4,1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 668, 2 of 4,1989 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 668, 3 of 4,1989 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 668, 4 of 4,1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 669,1988 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 670,1988 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 671, 1 of 5,1988 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 671, 2 of 5,1988 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 671, 3 of 5,1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 671, 4 of 5,1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 671, 5 of 5,1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 672,1988 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 672, 1 of 3,1989 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 672, 2 of 3,1989 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 672, 3 of 3,1989 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 673,1988 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 673, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 673, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 674, 1 of 3,1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 674, 2 of 3,1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 674, 3 of 3,1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 674,1989 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 675,1989 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 675,1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 676,1988 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 677,1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 678,1989 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 679,1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 680, 1 of 2,1989 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 680, 2 of 2,1989 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Daily Report, Job 681,1989 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 682,1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 683, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 683, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 683,1991 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 684, 1 of 31989 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 684, 2 of 31989 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 684, 3 of 31989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 686, 1 of 31989 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 686, 2 of 31989 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 686, 3 of 31989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 686,1990 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 686,1991 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 687,1989 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 688, 1 of 2,1990 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 688, 2 of 2,1990 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 689,1989 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 690, 1 of 3,1990 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 690, 2 of 3,1990 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 690, 3 of 3,1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 690,1991 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 691,1989 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 691,1990 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 691,1991 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 692,1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 692, 1 of 5,1990 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 692, 2 of 5,1990 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 692, 3 of 5,1990 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 692, 4 of 5,1990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 692, 5 of 5,1990 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 693,1990 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 694,1990 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 695,1990 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 696,1990 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 697,1990 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 698,1990 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 699,1990 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 700,1990 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 701, 1 of 4,1990 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Daily Report, Job 701, 2 of 4,1990 (Box 71, Folder 10)